Encounters are mysterious! But cases are even more so!
لقاءات البشر مغلّفة بالغموض، والقضايا تلفّها طبقات أكثر حتّى
I'm so glad I'm with you!
!أنا مسرورٌ حقّاً لكوني معك
Today is the mole solution! People's feelings connect underground!
!اليوم ختام قضيّة الخلد! مشاعر الناس مرتبطة تحت الأرض
He sees the single truth for what it is,
يرى الحقيقة الواحدة
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
يحمل مظهر طفل، لكنّ عقله عقل بالغ
His name? Detective Conan!
!اسمه المتحرّي كونان
Genta, Mitsuhiko, Ayumi, and I were playing baseball
كنتُ ألعب مع غينتا وميتسوهيكو وأيومي كرة القاعدة
in the parking lot of an unfinished apartment building.
في ساحة مواقف سيّارات لبناية شقق غير مكتملة
We went to get the ball after it landed in the yard next door,
ذهبنا لجلب الكرة بعدما سقطت في فناء منزل مجاور
but the house's owner, Watanuki Yoshikazu, sent us away.
لكن طردنا مالك المنزل، واتانوكي يوشيكازو
Waiting for us back at the detective agency was Koda Masao,
وعندما رجعنا لوكالة التحرّي، كان بانتظارنا
who looked just like the Mole Alien from Masked Yaiba.
كودا ماساو الذي بدا كفضائيّ الخلد في يايبا المقنّع
He claimed that his missing sister had been killed by Watanuki
قال أنّ شقيقته التي فُقدت قبل شهر قد قُتلت على يدَي واتانوكي
and buried somewhere in his yard, so he wanted help finding her.
،ودُفنت في مكانٍ ما في فنائه وطلب المساعدة في إيجادها
But sneaking onto others' property and digging things up is illegal.
لكنّ التسلّل لمنازل الآخرين والحفر في فنائهم أمرٌ مخالف للقانون
After his request was turned down, Koda Masao left angrily.
بعدما رفض العمّ طلبه، غادر كودا ماساو غاضباً
But, convinced he would dig up the yard
لكن، بعد اقتناعنا بأنّه سيحفر في الفناء
while Watanuki was at the hospital, we continued our stakeout!
!أثناء غياب واتانوكي في المشفى، واصلنا المراقبة
Just then, a jewel robbery took place!
!آنذاك، وقعت جريمة سطو على محلّ مجوهرات
And the robber was none other than Koda Masao!
!والسارق كان كودا ماساو نفسه
Just what is his true objective?!
ما هو دافعه الحقيقيّ؟
Saturday
السبت
What's taking the Mole Alien so long?
تأخّر فضائيّ الخلد
Come on, let's stop calling him that.
توقّف عن مناداته بذلك
He only looks like one.
فهو يبدو مثله لا أكثر
What? You're the one who first mentioned it!
!ماذا؟ أنتِ من أطلق ذلك عليه
It's him!
!إنّه هو
He really is a Mole Alien!
!كان فضائيّ الخلد بالفعل
What do we do, Genta-kun?!
ماذا نفعل يا غينتا-كن؟
Let's have a look for now!
!بأيّ حال، لنذهب وننظر
What's he doing?
ما الذي يفعله؟
Wasn't he going to dig up the yard?
ألم يكن سيحفر في الفناء؟
Then should I lend him my shovel?
!سأعيره مجرفتي إذاً
Wait. Let's watch a little longer...
انتظر، لنراقب أكثر
If my theory is correct, Koda-san is...
...إذا أصاب تحليلي، فكودا-سان
Beika Central Hospital
مشفى بيكا المركزيّ
What? No one called me?
ماذا؟ لم يتّصل بي أحد؟
That's right. We don't call patients about such things here.
أجل، لا نتّصل بالمرضى لأمور كهذه
Then who was that call from?
من كان المتّصل إذاً؟
Take me to 1st Street in Beika! Hurry!
!خذني لشارع بيكا الأوّل! أسرع رجاءً
R-Right!
!حـ-حاضر
Genta-kun! This is Mitsuhiko! Do you read me?!
غينتا-كن! معك ميتسوهيكو! أتسمعني؟
Team leader here! What's going on, Mitsuhiko?
معك القائد! ما الذي يجري يا ميتسوهيكو؟
Oh, brother. The old man just headed back there in a taxi!
مشكلة، غادر العجوز بسيّارة أجرة !وهو متّجه لكم
Got it!
فهمت
What now, Ayumi?
ماذا نفعل يا أيومي؟
It might be best to let him know.
ربما حريّ بنا إخباره
Hey! Mister! Watanuki-san is gonna be back soon!
!يا عمّ! واتانوكي-سان سيرجع قريباً
He's gonna see you if you don't hurry and run!
!سيراك إذا لم تسرع وتهرب
Conan-kun!
!كونان-كن
Just as I thought!
!كما ظننت
What do you mean, Conan?
ما قصدك يا كونان؟
Koda-san is--
...كودا-سان
Hey! What do you think you're doing?!
!أنت! ما الذي تظنّ أنّك تفعله؟
I'm about to prove what you did!
!أثبت ما قمتَ بارتكابه
What?
ماذا؟
Get out! Get out this instant! That goes for you, too!
!ارحل! فلتخرج من هنا فوراً! وأنتم كذلك
Yikes...
...مخيف
What's that?!
ما ذلك؟
Something's sparkling!
هناك شيءٌ يلمع
Sanae's earring!
!قرط ساناي
A glass shard...
...شظيّة زجاج
Damn it!
!تبّاً
I'll make the call for you, Mister.
سأجري أنا الاتّصال يا عمّ
You're turning yourself in, right? I know an inspector there!
ستسلّم نفسك للشرطة، صحيح؟ أعرف مفتّشاً هناك
Inspector Megure, correct? I've been expecting you.
مفتّش ميغوري، صحيح؟ كنتُ بانتظارك
What is this, Koda-san? Did you really commit a jewel robbery?
ما معنى هذا يا كودا-سان؟ أسطوت على محلّ مجوهرات حقّاً؟
Yes. The jewels I stole are buried throughout Watanuki's yard.
أجل، المجوهرات التي سرقتُها مدفونة في فناء واتانوكي
I don't remember where I buried them,
،لا أتذكّر أين دفنتها بالضبط
so you'll have to dig up the yard to find them.
فعليكم حفر الفناء والبحث عنها
What?!
!ماذا؟
What are all those holes?!
!ما هذه الحفر؟
Koda-san made them! The jewels are buried in some of them!
من صنع كودا-سان، المجوهرات مدفونةٌ في بعضٍ منها
So, you'll have to dig the whole yard up to find them all!
لذا عليكم حفر الفناء بأكمله لمعرفة أيّها تحوي المجوهرات
Koda-san!
!كودا-سان
Don't tell me you did the robbery to have the police dig up this yard?!
أيمكن أنّك أقدمت على عمليّة السطو تلك كي تدفع الشرطة للتنقيب في الفناء؟
Then you never intended to escape from the start?!
لم تنو الهرب من البداية إذاً؟
Koda-san just wanted enough time to dig holes in the yard.
أراد كودا-سان وقتاً كافياً لحفر الحفر لا أكثر
That's why he left a jewel on the station stairs
لذا تعمّد ترك جوهرة ،على أدراج المحطّة
and made it look like he escaped by train!
وأوهمنا أنّه هرب بالقطار
This is the model gun I used in the robbery.
هذا المسدّس المقلّد الذي استعملته في السطو
Watanuki Yoshikazu-san, correct?
أنت واتانوكي يوشيكازو-سان، صحيح؟
Yes.
أجل
Mori-kun there has told me about your incident with Koda-san.
أخبرني موري-كن هنا عن قضيّتك مع كودا-سان
Do you mind if we dig up your yard?
هل تمانع حفرنا في الفناء؟
Y-You can't be serious! What gives you the right?!
لا-لا تمازحني! أيّ حقّ لديكم؟
It's absolutely necessary for the investigation of the jewel robbery.
هذا ضروريّ لإتمام تحقيقات عملية سطو
Or is there some reason digging up your yard would be bad for you?
أم قد يخرج ما يضرّك إن حفرنا الفناء؟
O-Of course not!
!بـ-بالطبع لا
In that case... Takagi-kun! Contact headquarters!
!في تلك الحالة، تاكاغي-كن، اتّصل بالمركز
Yes, sir!
!حاضر
Alright!
!رائع
Good for you, Mister!
هذا حسنٌ لك يا عمّ
Yeah!
أجل
What's that smile for?! Don't tell me he--?!
...لمَ هذه الابتسامة؟ أيمكن
The jewels are quite small! Dig everything up!
!المجوهرات صغيرة! فلتحفروا المكان كليّاً
Inspector!
!حضرة المفتّش
Only the jewels have turned up.
لم نجد سوى المجوهرات
I don't think there are any bodies buried here...
لا أظنّ أنّه توجد أيّ جثث هنا
That can't be!
!يستحيل ذلك
Look harder!
!أمعنوا البحث
We are looking hard! Where else are we supposed to dig?!
أمعنّا البحث! أين يُفترض بنا الحفر في غير هذا؟
Maybe I should use this opportunity to start a vegetable garden.
ربما سأستغلّ هذه الفرصة في زراعة حديقة خضروات
Right, Inspector?
صحيح، حضرة المفتّش؟
Dammit!
!تبّاً
Koda-san!
!كودا-سان
Koda-san...
...كودا-سان
Shut up! Sanae is here! I know she's buried in this yard somewhere!
اخرس! ساناي هنا! إنّها مدفونة !في مكانٍ ما في هذا الفناء حتماً
I can understand how you feel, but there's no point in continuing this.
أتفهّم شعورك، لكن لا جدوى من مواصلة هذا
Sanae...
...ساناي
Sanae!
!ساناي
The police took Koda-san into custody?!
اعتقلت الشرطة كودا-سان؟
Yeah, no matter what his reason, he did commit a jewel robbery.
أجل، فقد ارتكب عمليّة سطو على محلّ مجوهرات مهما كانت دوافعه
But why didn't the body turn up?
لكن لمَ لم يجدوا الجثّة؟
Because there was never one to begin with.
لأنّها لم تكن موجودةً من البداية
Koda-san was mistaken.
أخطأ كودا-سان الظنّ
Watanuki-san didn't kill her; she went missing for some other reason.
لم يقتلها واتانوكي-سان، بل اختفت لسببٍ آخر
No! Watanuki-san definitely killed her!
!كلا، قتلها واتانوكي-سان
That smile then...
...ابتسامته آنذاك
That look was more proof than anything!
!كانت أكبر دليل
But it's a fact she said she was going to visit Watanuki-san's house
لكنّها قالت أنّها ستزور منزل واتانوكي-سان
before heading home on the night of May 8th, right?
قبل الرجوع للبيت في ليلة الثامن من مايو بلا شكّ، صحيح؟
Yeah, that's what her co-worker said.
أجل، هذا ما قاله زميلها في العمل
Eh? You went to her company? Did you find anything out?!
ماذا؟ ذهبت لشركتها يا عمّ؟ هل اكتشفت شيئاً؟
The only other thing I learned
الشيء الوحيد الإضافيّ الذي اكتشفته
was that that co-worker gave her some cosmos seeds during lunch.
هو أنّ زميلها أعطاها بذور قسموس في استراحة الغداء
Cosmos seeds?
بذور قسموس؟
Yeah, don't you remember? Koda-san said she loved cosmos flowers.
ألا تذكرين؟ قال أنّ أخته تحبّ أزهار القسموس
Anyways, the most likely possibility
بأيّ حال، أكبر احتمالٍ الآن
is that she was caught up in some incident and went missing
هو أنّ حادثاً ما وقع لها فاختفت
on her way to Watanuki-san's house from her company.
في طريقها لمنزل واتانوكي-سان بعد مغادرتها للشركة
Supposedly, the police are going to investigate from that angle, too.
يبدو أنّ الشرطة ستعتمد تحقيقها على ذلك الأساس أيضاً
The next day (Sunday)
(اليوم التالي (الأحد
Then you think that old man killed her, Conan-kun?
تعتقد أنّ ذاك العجوز قد قتلها إذاً يا كونان-كن؟
Yeah, I'm almost certain of it.
أجل، أنا متأكّد من الأمر تقريباً
But they never found her body.
لكنّهم لم يجدوا جثّتها
Hmm, maybe it was buried under a floorboard instead of the garden?
أجل، ربما دُفنت تحت لوح أرضيّة في المنزل وليس الحديقة؟
No. There wouldn't have been a digging sound in the back alley.
كلا، لن يُسمع صوت حفر في الزقاق الخلفيّ في تلك الحالة
Hey, let's check out the library.
هل نذهب للمكتبة؟
L-Library?
الـ-المكتبة؟
Yeah!
أجل
If we check the newspapers from May 8th, we might find something!
،إذا تفقّدنا صحف الثامن من مايو !قد نكتشف شيئاً
Yeah! But we don't want to check newspapers from the 8th.
معكِ حقّ، لكن ما علينا تفقّده ليست صحف الثامن من مايو
Because news from the night of the 8th won't be in that day's paper.
لأنّ أنباء تلك الليلة لن تظهر في صحيفة اليوم نفسه
There's a Masked Yaiba show at Toto Dept. Store the 23rd and 24th!
يوجد عرض ليايبا المقنّع في مركز تسوّق توتو !يوما الثالث والعشرين والرابع والعشرين
We gotta see it!
!علينا الذهاب لمشاهدته
Genta-kun. You're reading last month's paper.
غينتا-كن، أنت تقرأ صحف الشهر الفائت
Not to mention, we all went to that show!
كما أنّنا ذهبنا جميعاً لمشاهدة ذاك العرض
Oh, really?
حقّاً؟
Yes, really!
!أجل، حقّاً
I don't see any pertinent articles...
لا أرى أيّ مقالات ذات صلة
Conan-kun.
كونان-كن
There was a strong easterly wind from the night of the 8th to the 9th.
كانت هناك ريح شرقيّة قويّة من ليلة اليوم الثامن إلى التاسع وفقما يبدو
What's that got to do with this case?
ما علاقة ذلك بالقضيّة؟
No, I don't know...
...حسناً، لستُ متأكداً
There don't seem to be any clues here,
،يبدو أنّه لا توجد أيّ دلائل قد تفيدنا
so let's go see the Mochida-san person who heard the digging sound!
فلمَ لا نذهب للقاء موتشيدا-سان الذي سمع صوت الحفر؟
lt was a month ago, and I was drunk,
كان ذلك قبل شهر، وكنتُ ثملاً
Mochida Shinichi (35)
(موتشيدا شينتشي (35
so I don't remember clearly.
فلا أتذكّر بوضوح
You entered the alley from this road, right?
دخلت الزقاق من هذا الطريق، صحيح؟
Yeah, there was loud construction on this road that night.
أجل، كان صوت عمليات البناء على هذا الطريق مزعجاً تلك الليلة
So I hurried into this alley, and lit a cigarette a little ways down.
فأسرعتُ لهذا الزقاق، وأشعلت سيجارة بعدما مشيت فيه قليلاً
That's when I heard a shovel by the house to the left.
عندها سمعت صوت مجرفة من المنزل يساراً
You're certain it was this house?
أأنت متأكّد أنّه كان هذا المنزل؟
Well, I was drunk, so...
...حسناً، كنت ثملاً
Yeah. I'm certain of it. I heard it coming from my left.
أجل، أنا متأكّد، سمعتُه من يساري
Could you act out what you did again?
هلّا قلّدتَ ما فعلته ليلتها؟
Yeah, okay.
لا أمانع
There was a construction truck parked there.
كانت هناك شاحنة تابعة لعمليات البناء مركونةً هناك
So I went into the alley while thinking what a nuisance it was.
فدخلتُ الزقاق وأنا أتذمّر من إزعاجها
Yeah, it was around here where I lit my cigarette.
أجل، أشعلتُ سيجارتي في هذه النقطة تقريباً
Wait a minute! This way is east!
!انتظر، هذا الشرق
Say! Was there a strong wind coming straight at you?!
أخبرني، ألم تهبّ عليك رياح قويّة مباشرةً وقتها؟
Oh, now that you mention it...
...بذكرك ذلك
The wind was so strong it kept putting out the lighter,
كانت الرياح قويّة، فانطفأت شعلة القدّاحة من فورها
Main Road West Apartments East Watanuki's Home
بناية الشقق
so I turned around to light it.
فاستدرتُ لإشعالها
Huh? Does that mean...
...لحظة، أيعني ذلك
Left was right, and right was left?
كان اليسار يميناً، واليمين يساراً؟
Conan-kun!
!كونان-كن
Oh! So that's why he--!
...فهمت! لذا آنذاك
Alright! This manhole will be the home plate!
حسنٌ، ستكون فتحة الصرف هذه !هي القاعدة الرئيسيّة
All right! I figured it out!
!حسناً! وجدتها
Eh?! You know where the body is?!
ماذا؟ عرفتم مكان الجثّة؟
Yes! We, the Junior Detective League, found it!
!أجل! وجدناها نحن، فرقة فتيان التحرّي
So, where is it?!
أخبروني أين إذاً؟
Forget 'em. The brats are obviously spewing nonsense.
دعيكِ منهم، ما يقوله هؤلاء الأطفال هراءٌ بلا شكّ
But Shinichi-niichan said there was no doubt about it, too!
لكن قال شينتشي-نيتشان أنّ لا شكّ في الأمر أيضاً
What?!
!ماذا؟
You saw Shinichi, Conan-kun?!
!التقيت شينتشي يا كونان-كن؟
No, I talked to him on the phone just now!
كلا، كلّمته على الهاتف قبل قليل
He said he would call Inspector Megure!
وقال أنّه سيتّصل بالمفتّش ميغوري
So, you two should come along!
!لذا عليكما القدوم أيضاً
Come along where?
إلى أين؟
What is this about, Inspector?! I'd like an explanation!
ما الذي يجري يا حضرة المفتّش؟ هلّا شرحت لي؟
R-Right...
...حـ-حسناً
Are you kids really sure about this?
أأنتم متأكدون مما تفعلونه؟
I never would've agreed to this had Shinichi-kun not called me...
لم أكن لأوافق على فعل هذا ...لو لم يتّصل بي شينتشي-كن البتّة
Leave it to us, Inspector!
دع الأمر لنا حضرة المفتّش
Okay, let's begin!
!حسناً، لنبدأ
The night of May 8th, Koda-san's sister, Sanae-san,
،في ليلة الثامن من مايو، مرّت ساناي-سان
stopped by this house after work, just like she had said.
أخت كودا-سان، بهذا المنزل بعد مغادرتها الشركة كما قالت
And, just as Koda-san surmises...
،وكما استنتج كودا-سان
...Watanuki-san killed her.
فقد قتلها واتانوكي-سان
Ridiculous! What nonsense! They dug up the entire yard yesterday!
سخافة! أيّ هراء تقوله؟ !حفروا الفناء بأكمله بالأمس
But you buried the body not in your yard, but somewhere else!
!لكنّك لم تدفن الجثّة في فنائك، بل مكان آخر
Tell me! Where is my sister buried?!
!أخبرني! أين دُفنت أختي؟
The answer to that is upstairs!
!ستعرفون إذا ذهبتم للطابق العلويّ
Follow me!
اتبعوني
Hey! Wait!
!لحظة، انتظروا
Hey, Conan! Where in this room could she be?!
كونان، أين دُفنت في هذه الغرفة؟
She's not in here.
ليس هنا
Here!
بل هنا
What's that?
ما هذا؟
An unfinished apartment building.
بناية شقق غير مكتملة
Your sister's body is buried there.
جثّة أختك مدفونة هناك
At the time of the incident, its construction was going as scheduled.
وقت الحادثة، كانت عمليات البناء تجري وفق المخطط
Burying a body there would mean it wouldn't be dug up for decades.
لذا دفن جثّةٍ هناك يعني أنّها لن تُستخرج لعقود
This fact was a relief to him.
أشعره ذلك بالارتياح
But something unexpected happened half a month later.
لكن وقع أمرٌ خارج التوقعات بعد نصف شهر
The apartments' construction was suddenly canceled.
أُلغيت عمليات البناء فجأةً
Eh?! Then they're going to be demolished?!
ماذا؟! أي سيهدمونه؟
It's very possible. And the body would be found right away.
ذلك مُحتمل، وستُكتشف الجثّة فوراً
I'm so worried I can't sleep at night!
!أنا أشعر بالقلق فلا أستطيع النوم ليلاً
Let's watch the place with binoculars!
!لأراقب المكان بالمنظار
And that's why Watanuki-san stopped leaving the house
لذا توقّف واتانوكي-سان عن مغادرة المنزل
for everything but hospital visits.
باستثناء مواعيده في المشفى
And it's why he watched the premises with these binoculars.
وكان يراقب محيط البناية بهذا المنظار
But I have no way to enter those premises!
!لكنّي لا أستطيع دخول محيطها
The area is fenced off, and the gate was locked that night!
يحيطها السياج، وكانت البوابة مقفلة تلك الليلة
You speak as if you investigated these things.
تتكلّم كما لو أنّك تحرّيت ذلك سلفاً
But there's a hole in the back!
!لكن توجد فتحة في الخلف
No, that was made just recently.
كلا، نشأت تلك مؤخراً
Conan, how did he get in there?
كونان، كيف دخل هناك؟
Koda-san has the answer to that.
يعرف كودا-سان إجابة ذلك
By sheer coincidence, he used the exact same method!
كان الأمر محض مصادفة، لكنّه استعمل الطريقة نفسها
You mean...?!
...أيمكن
Oh!
!هكذا إذاً
I get it!
!فهمت
The sewer system!
!شبكة التصريف
That night, there was a construction truck parked in the alley,
كانت هناك شاحنة تابعة لعمليات البناء مركونة في الزقاق تلك الليلة
so this house's back entrance couldn't be seen from the main street.
فلم يكن ممكناً رؤية مدخل هذا المنزل الخلفيّ من الشارع الرئيسيّ
I see! So the sewer system connects here!
!فهمت! شبكة التصريف مرتبطة هنا
The night of May 8th, major construction covered the main street,
ليلة الثامن من مايو، كانت هناك عمليات بناء كبيرة على الشارع الرئيسيّ
so the sound of a shovel digging wouldn't seem suspicious to anyone.
فصوت حفر بمجرفة لن يثير غرابة أيّ أحد
To anyone but Mochida-san, that is.
باستثناء موتشيدا-سان بالطبع
Isn't that right, Watanuki-san?
ألستُ محقّاً يا واتانوكي-سان؟
Damn you!
!أيّها الوغد
Why did you kill Sanae?!
!لمَ قتلتَ ساناي؟
Stop it!
!توقّف
D-Do you have proof?!
!أ-ألديكم دليل؟
This is all nothing but that child's conjecture!
!كلّ هذا مجرّد افتراضات لذاك الصبيّ
So what if I could've entered this parking lot?!
وماذا إذا استطعت دخول !ساحة المواقف هذه؟
Anyone could've used that method to get in here!
كان بإمكان أيّ أحد الدخول هنا !باستعمال تلك الطريقة
And besides, where is the body anyway?!
كما أين الجثّة بالأصل؟
Right here.
هنا
The body of Koda-san's sister is resting beneath this plant.
جثّة أخت كودا-سان هي أسفل هذه الزهرة
What?!
!ماذا؟
But, Conan-kun! How do you know it's here?!
لكن يا كونان-كن، كيف تعرف أنّها هنا؟
Look!
انظروا
A cosmos...
...قسموس
Oh, yeah! A coworker gave your sister some cosmos seeds that day!
فهمت! تلقّت أختك بذور قسموس !من أحد زملائها ذاك اليوم
And one must've fallen out and sprouted after she was buried...
أي سقطت تلك البذور وتبرعمت ...بعدما دُفنت إذاً
I didn't mean to kill her...
لم أنو قتلها
I snapped that night when she refused to compensate me...
...فقدتُ أعصابي تلك الليلة عندما رفضت تعويضي
Then our deal is off!
!صفقتنا ملغيّة إذاً
Leave!
ارحلي
W-Wait! Watanuki-san!
!ا-انتظر رجاءً! واتانوكي-سان
Watanuki-san!
!واتانوكي-سان
Shut up!
!اخرسي
Sanae...
...ساناي
That night, his sister's body was found beneath the cosmos seedling.
في تلك الليلة، وُجدت جثّة الأخت أسفل شتلة القسموس
After that, Koda-san was given a suspended sentence for his robbery.
لاحقاً، تمّ إيقاف تنفيذ حكم جريمة السطو لكودا-سان، وأُطلق سراحه
He decided to return to his hometown with the cosmos seedling.
قرّر العودة إلى بلدته الأمّ مع شتلة القسموس
It won't bring his sister back,
،لن ترجع أخته
but he said he'll take great care of it, as if it were her.
لكنّه قال أنّه سيعتني بهذه الشتلة كما لو كانت هي
And thus the mystery of the Mole Alien was solved!
!وهكذا حُلّ لغز قضيّة فضائيّ الخلد
By the way, Conan-kun.
...بالمناسبة يا كونان-كن
Yes, Ran-neechan?
ماذا يا ران-نيتشان؟
You said you talked to Shinichi on the phone, right?
قلتَ أنّك كلمّت شينتشي على الهاتف، صحيح؟
Y-Yeah...
...أ-أجل
Uh oh!
!هذا سيّئ
Tell me... where is he?
أخبرني، أين هو؟
Oh, uhh, actually...
...أ-أنا، ذلك
Answer me, Conan-kun!
!أجبني يا كونان-كن
She's scarier than Mole Aliens!
!إنّها مخيفة أكثر من فضائيّ الخلد
Hey! A car's coming!
انتبهي، هناك سيّارة قادمة
Ayumi! Damn!
...أيومي! تبّاً
Ishikura-san's killer was you, Shishido-san!
!من قتل إيشيكورا-سان كانت أنت يا شيشيدو-سان
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
Say it with me. Next Conan's hint:
سويّاً، تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Muddy water.
وحل
On the next episode—
...الحلقة القادمة
It's your fault, Genta-kun!
!إنّها غلطة غينتا-كن !فلتتحمّل المسؤولية
What did you do?
!ما الذي فعلتَه؟
I'm screwed.
!غينتا-كن في مأزق